前情提要
Previously on Lost Girl...
Lauren似乎加入了黑暗派
Lauren, it looks like she's gone with the Dark.
我也一样
So did I.
没事的Bo
You're going to be okay, Bo
现在你是也黑暗派了
now that you're dark.
我们以后天天见
I'll see you around.
你不需要是异种才能成为我们的一员
You don't have to be Fae to have a place among us.
我可以教你
I can teach you.
我还是不相信你
Still don't trust you.
你已经是黑暗那一边的了
You are Team Dark now.
法典被破坏了
The codex of laws have been infringed upon.
不是你 是他
Not you, him.
小子 你在哪呢
Where you at, boy?
Hale!
Dyson在哪?
Where's Dyson?
Una Mens还扣押着呢
Una Mens still have him.
防守严密 谁也进不去
Security is full throttle,  no one's getting in.
一个和尚给我脖子上来了一拳
I took a punch. To the neck. By a monk.
噢  亲
Aw, Baby.
没事的 亲
Oh, wow, okay.
要是能让他开口 我们就能找到Dyson
Our key to getting to Dyson.If we can get him to talk.
我那个失足妇女案子的知情人
Informants. For my sex worker case.
干嘛 你们以前没玩过抓和尚吗？
What, like you guys never play "Captured Monk" before?
来点刺激的 39师
Spice it up, thirty ninth division!
为什么只抓了Dyson
Why take only Dyson when we both broke Fae law
我俩不是都睡了对方
by sleeping together?!
为啥你的魅力不管用了
What's with the no-glow?!
肯定是个太监
Must be a eunuch.
你是说……
You mean ... ?
恩 沙滩靓女排球对他们也没用的
Mm-hmm. Not even beach volleyball won't do it for 'em.
看来我们得用点传统手段
Looks like we gotta do this the old fashioned way.
你行的兄弟
Yea boyeee.
搞定他
Get 'em.
我来问 你来答
I'm gonna ask questions and you're gonna have answers.
谁在审判席上为Dyson出庭？
Who is representing Dyson at his trial?!
不好意思 太大声了吗?
I'm sorry, was that too loud for you?
你以前见过海妖吗?
Did you ever meet a Siren before?
快回答问题 否则......
Start talking or...
* Oppilo 拉丁文中停止的意思*
停止
Oppilo!
说英语
English.
拜托
Please.
赶快交待
Talk. Fast.
没有审判
There is no trial.
只有处刑
There is execution.
就因为和黑暗派滚了床单
For sleeping with Dark Fae?!
因为谋反
For treason.
1899年 狼叔冷酷的谋杀了人类和异种
In 1899, the Wolf murdered humans and Fae in cold blood.
我才不管他活了多久
I don't care how long he's been alive.
那绝对不是Dyson
That's not Dyson.
是啊
Yeah.
去告诉你那些和尚赶紧让路
Now you tell your monks to clear the way
让我们进去
so we can get to The Keeper and Funky Bunch.
走吧
Let's go.
回归虚无
Convertimini ad nihilum.
*拉丁文*
*指世界上无人再使用拉丁文做母语*
真是忠诚
Loyal little shit.
拉丁文已死
Latin is a dead language.
我们还能怎么办 Trick？
What are our other options? What about Trick?
不 他们不会让他旁观的
Nah, they won't grant him audience.
Una Mens送他去搞代理Ash的是了
Una Mens sent him away on acting Ash duty.
总有点什么我能做的吧
Well, there has to be something that we can do.
来吧小伙伴们
Come on, Worry Watsons.
他们不会真的杀狼叔吧
They're not actually going to kill D-Man...
会吗?
Are they?
求你们了
I'm begging you.
你们抓错清道夫了
You have the wrong scavenger.
*拉丁文*
死亡
Mortis.
吾寻之
Invenio.
大一统
In unitate.
你没能遵守神圣的异种法律
You have failed to abide by the sacred rules of the Fae.
还有什么遗言 赶快说吧
If you have last words, speak them now.
不 别
No. Please ... don't.
不 求你们了 别
No,Please, please don't.
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  r(st)q
英文字幕：来自互联网
翻译：Neffititi  骷髅头正宫_K
精校：Neffititi  骷髅头正宫_K  Joy  李夹碎
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
4x07 - "La Fae Epoque"
我们还有多少时间?
How much time do we have?
一小时
An hour.
五分钟
Five minutes.
我不知道
I don't know.
多谢你过来
Thank you for coming.
我当然要来
Of course I came.
我不知道嘛最近
But I don't know, lately.
我是说 你现在都跟黑暗混
I mean, you're with the Dark.
狼可是光明派
Dyson's Light.
狼是家人
Dyson's family.
我以前救过他 现在也一样
I've saved him before, I'd do it again.
到底发生了啥?
How did this happen?
我们正在那啥的时候他们出现了......
They caught us while we were...
啥？
What?
哦 我懂
Oh. I get the picture.
怎么！你和m女王还不是搞得很亲热
So! You and The Morrigan are getting close.
看来Kenzi跟你说了啊
I see Kenzi reported back.
不是
No! It's not that.
只是你持有的这些装置
It's just that you have all this equipment.
她知道是为了救Dyson吗?
Does she know it's to save Dyson?
我不知道
I don't know.
我又没问 就拿了
I don't ask. I just take.
想想黑暗派会怎么干就对了
It's sort of a think Dark to be Dark kinda thing.
哎哟 嘿
Oh. Hello.
对不起
Sorry.
不用道歉
Don't be.
*一种用大豆油提取的蜡制作的蜡烛*
真是温馨
How heartwarming.
接下来要干嘛 豆油蜡烛？
What's next, soy candles?
*加拿大乐队 成员为一对双胞胎*
再来点Tegan和Sara?
A little Tegan and Sara?
赶紧的
Let's go!
老娘还有地方要去 有人要交流
I've got places to be, people to channel.
先知按小时收费很贵的 你懂?
An Oracle's time isn't cheap, you know?
是的 Cassie 我们知道
Yeah, Cassie. We know.
Trick费老大劲才把你拉了来
Trick pulled serious strings to get you here.
他欠我的简直数不胜数
He's owes me like, infinity.
他来干涉真是意外
Surprised he intervened.
要是被发现他也是个死
He gets caught, they execute him too.
那我们到底要干嘛?
So what's the plan?
你要帮我进入Dyson的记忆
You need to get me into Dyson's memory.
他因为一件陈年案子被诬陷了
He's being framed for a billion year old murder.
你要证明他是无辜的
And I have to prove he's innocent.
我还以为你要叫我看看
For a second I thought you were gonna ask me to look into that
你的记忆里各种黑洞
gaping black hole in your memory.
不可能......就连我都不行
Impossible... even for me.
你能看见黑洞？
You can see it?
你知道的 几年前咱俩一面之缘
You know, after our reading few years back,
我还以为你就是那个人
I thought you might be "The One".
不结盟的淫妖带领异种走向新时代
The unaligned Succubus, fighting to lead  the Fae into a new era...
看来没戏
Guess not.
压轴的东西
The final element.
你特么在逗我？
Are you shizering me?
命运的红线？
The Red String of Fate?
*一种治疗精神病的手术*
你还不如直接切除她的前脑叶白质呢!
You might as well lobotomize Bo right now!
不然你有何高见？
You have a better idea?
Dyson又不在这
Dyson's remote.
只有这办法了
It's the only way.
传说神将这些红线栓在
According to legend the gods used to wrap this
有缘人的脚踝上
around the ankles of those destined to meet.
不论时间地点情况 他们终会相见
Regardless of time,place, or circumstance.
这会让你和Bo跟Dyson的连接更牢固
It'll secure your connection to Bo and to Dyson.
我会在这......作为常量
I'll stay here ... the constant.
真不错 Lewis医生
That's beautiful, Doctor Lewis.
你要进入Dyson的记忆 但你的潜意识
You'll gonna go into Dyson's memory, but your subconscious
还是在现在 你可能会投射熟悉的地方
will stay present. You'll likely project familiar places
和人物到Dyson的过往
and people that you know into Dyson's past.
剧透下 我会出现
Spoiler alert: I'll make an appearance.
我一出现我们就得走
And when I do, it's time to get out.
要不你的记忆就会和Dyson的融合
Or risk fusing your memories with Dyson's.
啥意思?
Meaning?
你会疯
You'll go clinically insane.
我以前见过病例
I've seen it happen.
永久性的
It's permanent.
而且不怎么舒服
And not pretty.
你在这个险冒得很大你知道吗 Bo
You're putting yourself in major danger here, Bo.
你确定你要这样做？
Are you sure you wanna do this?
为了你我也会冒险的
I would do the same for you.
那 现在呢？
So, now what?
我们等着和Dyson建立连接
We wait for a connection to Dyson...
嘘
Shh.
继续洗
Keep washing him.
太好了 Kenzi搞定了
Yes! Yes! Kenzi did it, it's working!
就这样 深呼吸
This is it. You're gonna want to take a deep breath
是谁？
C'est qui?
开门！出来！
Ouvre la porte, Salir!!!
他在哪？
Where is he?
我爱他 我爱他
I love him! I love him!
这个开口容不下一个男人
This opening is too small for a man.
Dyson 你这邪魅帅哥
Dyson, you handsome devil.
他在这！
There he is!
我的女儿
My daughters.
我宝贵的女儿
My precious daughters.
宝贵 还很有说服力
Precious, and... persuasive.
你知道 作为她们的爹 你应该知道......
You know,As their father,you should know...
你敢！
Don't you dare.
我的错
My apologies.
你看上去不像坏人
You... seem like a noble man.
你老婆对你评价很高
Your wife speaks very highly of you.
你认识Isabelle？
You know Isabelle?
你太过分了
You have gone too far.
祝你在地狱过得愉快
I hope you enjoy hell.
对不起
Excusez-moi?
长棍？
A bo staff?
在这可不太常见 您怎么称呼?
That's unusual in these parts, Monsieur..?
想要庇护就跟我来
Follow me if you want sanctuary.
*一种暖发酵的啤酒 又称麦芽酒*
庇护所提供爱尔啤酒吗？
Does this sanctuary serve ale?
你的名声在外
You have quite the reputation.
小偷 骗子
Thief. Con.
花花公子
Philanderer.
很沾沾自喜是吧?
You are proud of this?
好玩
Tickled.
法国人就是爱八卦
Look, we both know the French like to talk.
不光是法国
Not just the French.
你在全欧洲都臭名昭著
You're infamous throughout Europe.
好吧 我现在可是相当得意了
Okay, now I'm proud.
你很强 Dyson
You're powerful, Dyson.
你有潜力 可以更好
Capable of more. Of good.
你的袍子闻起来像萝卜
Alternately, your robe smells like turnips.
我还得去会个农夫的老婆呢
And I'm late for a rendezvous with a farmer's wife.
白白了 疯子
So farewell, crazy.
*北欧习俗 死人穿上这双鞋便可前往死后世界*
听着 那双Helskor
You will listen! The Helskor!
*Hel 北欧神话中与地狱同名的女神 掌管地狱 *
最强大的异种在找的古老的Hel鞋
The ancient Hel-shoes, sought after by the most powerful Fae.
包括流浪者……
Including The One Who Wanders...
我听得多了
I've heard the tales.
流血打仗
Wars waged. Blood shed.
只有配得上的英雄才能穿
They can only be worn by The Worthy Hero.
据说一个王子发现了他们
It is rumored that a Prince has uncovered them.
要卖给出价最高的买家
Selling them to the highest bidder.
在坏人拿到前你得截下来
You must intercept them before they fall into the wrong hands.
据说它们可以引领你去末日
It is said that they can lead to the end of days.
那我能有啥好处?
What do I get?
你要啥?
What do you want?
法郎
Francs.
你真的要啥?
What do you really you want?
你到底是谁?
Who are you?
Fitzpatrick McCorrigan
Fitzpatrick McCorrigan.
多谢有关鞋子的情报了......Trick
Thanks for the tip on the shoes... Trick.
鞋子......鞋子
Shoes... shoes...
挤奶女工  咪咪
Milkmaids. Boobs.
Dyson可真是斯文人
Oh. It's good to know Dyson was an intellectual.
Hel鞋
Hel-shoes.
长棍！
Bo staff!
Trick Trick
Trick. Trick.
一个无厘头宴会 我们都去
It's a non-sequitur party, and we're all invited.
Bo  你在说胡话啊
Bo, you're not making any sense.
流浪者
He who wanders.
啥？你说啥了？你刚说啥了？
What? What was that? What was that?
Helskor
Helskor.
接着说流浪者啊Bo 快点
What else about the The Wanderer, Bo? Come on.
咪咪
Boobs.
好吧 咪咪吧
Okay. Boobs it is.
走着进来 飞升出去
Enter on your feet and leave on a cloud!
欢迎来到天堂歌厅
Bienvenue au Cabaret Du Ciel!
真是天堂样
Heavenly.
你到了个美梦可以成真的
You have entered a place where dreams come true,
平行空间
outside of time and space.
来杯饮料
Grab a beverage.
然后来个天使
Hmm. Grab an angel.
该飞了
It is time to fly!
我的饮料呢
Where's my drink?
混蛋 乐趣都被你搞没了
Oh, Connard. You take all the fun out of my job.
好大的记忆裂痕？
Memory glitch much?
一点逻辑都没有诶
That doesn't make any sense...
今晚似乎每人都想分杯王子的羹
Everyone seems to want a piece of Le Prince tonight.
特别是那边那个
Especially face over there.
真是迷人
What a charmer.
叫他自己Crater
Calls himself Crater.
是来做生意的
Here on "business".
包打听的天使
An Angel with her ear to the ground.
继续
Go on...
旅行的王子 有钱 想找乐子
Traveling Prince. Great fortune. Seeks excitement.
就等着主角登场 都不带看我们一眼的
Ignores la plus pas barmaid as he waits the main attraction!
你知道吗?
You know who?
她没以前那么吸引人了
She does not attract the crowd she used to, hm?
那些人都不知道错过了什么
They don't know what they're missing...
抢在王子前头去她闺房
Get to her boudoire before The Prince does...
马上！表演时间！
Vite! Showtime!
女士们先生们
Madames et Monsieurs...
*Flora Blooms 字面意思为开花*
为你们隆重呈上 Flora Blooms小姐
Let me present to you...Madmoiselle Flora Blooms.
感谢潜意识
Thanks subconscious.
好微妙
Subtle.
看来Dyson也满享受嘛
Looks like Dyson's enjoying it too.
不不不
No no. No!
Flora和Lauren综合体还没唱完呢
Flora slash Lauren isn't done singing yet.
还是用的法语
In French!
他是殖民地里正直的市民
He is an upstanding citizen of this colony.
是光明派的保护者
A protector of The Light.
也是凶手
And a murderer.
他差点将我们暴露于人类之中
He risked revealing our kind to humans.
狼人要为了他的罪而被处决
The Wolf will be killed for his crimes.
作为前任Ash和Zamora家族的继承人
As former Ash and heir to the Zamora clan,
我要提醒你Dyson救了许多人的命
may I remind you that Dyson has fought for many lives.
打败了迦楼罗
Helped defeat the Garuda.
为救我们的人不要命
Risked his life for our people!
你一定要考虑
You have to consider.
我们考虑了
We consider.
我们驳回
We refute.
你可以走了
You are dismissed.
这就是你们所谓的公正？和平？
Is this what you call justice? Peace?
我受够这法西斯了！
I have had it with this fascism.
异种受够你们了
The Fae have had enough!
总有一天我们站起来当家做主
Soon they will rise above!And they will rule themselves!
艾玛 我不是调到震动了吗?
Oops.I swear I had it on vibrate.
你带了个人类进我们的密室？
You have brought a human into our chambers?
这真是最难堪的侮辱
Of your many insults,this is the most galling.
Kenzi
Kenzi.
不 别啊
No! No no no!
Una Mens 别关他 关我吧
Una Mens! Lock me up, not him!
狼的行刑继续执行
Proceed with the Wolf's execution.
这个人类也一起
And the human will join him.
赶紧的 Bo
Come on, Bo.
找到Dyson的不在场证明然后赶紧出来
Find those Dyson's alibi and get out of there.
你行的
You can do this...
都好几周了
It's been weeks.
你跑哪去了?
Where have you been?
你在乎？
You care?
当然不了
No. Of course I don't.
你得走了
You need to leave.
那个王子似乎在谋划什么
Something's afoot with our Prince.
我的阴谋偷盗计划也一样
Hence my heavy agenda of scheming and stealing.
快走吧
Now go.
这王子可不只有钱
This Prince carries more than just coin.
继续
Go on...
还有Helskor
Helskor.
荒谬
C'est ridicule!
那是不存在的好吗?
They don't exist.
存在
Or they do.
而且王子拿到它们了
And the Prince is in possession of them.
想想
Imagine.
我们能卖多少钱啊
Imagine how much we could get for them.
成千上万 或者更多
Thousands. Maybe more...
你终于可以赎身退休了
You could finally hang up your floral brassiere.
时代变了
Times are changing.
一个时代的结束
The end of an era.
再见了 美好时代
Adieu, La Belle Epoque!
你知道吗 那些人看我的眼光都变了
You know, the people don't look at me like they used to.
你说啥呢
Now you're just fishing.
他们爱你
They adore you.
不 他们看到的只是幻觉
Non. They see an illusion.
廉价的幻觉
A cheap illusion.
他们不懂我
They don't really know me.
但你知道吗 要是我们成功了
But you know...if we pull this off...
我就能回去格尔尼卡的树下草地
I could return to the tree of Gernika. To my grass.
*西班牙小镇 二战被德军空袭 后毕加索创作同名油画*
我的草地
My meadows...
*西班牙地名*
你还能把巴斯克的森林也买回来...
You could buy back your Basque forest…
舞厅倒是会少了个Leshii
This Cabaret will miss having a Leshii Fae around.
*斯拉夫地区保护森林的传说生物*
他们再找一个森林精灵勾引富人就是了
They can find another woodland spirit to seduce the rich.
这就是我的出路
This is my way out.
但是你知道吗 我可能会想念这些酒鬼
But you know...I might miss the perks.
对你来说我就是个酒鬼？
Is that what I am to you? Hmm? A perk?
你拿来的情报 我们就平分利润好了
Since you came with the tip, we'll split the profits.
五五分
Fifty-fifty.
然后一起跑
Then flee together.
这样旅途上我可以保护你
So I can protect you on your travels.
我才不要你的保护
I don't need your protection.
要是你愿意和我一起 探索我的领地
But if you want to join me, explore my land...
恩 就发生了？
So... this is happening.
是为了调查的对吧?
For... investigative purposes. Right?
对
Right.
呼吸不匀
Breathing is irregular.
心跳加快
Heart rate is increasing.
真的有点快
Slightly rapid.
你看到啥了
What are you seeing in there?
恩 真的吗？
Hmm.Really?
巧克力酱
Chocolate spread?
就不能像别人一样来点花生酱？
You can't have get peanut butter like everybody else?
Lauren......
Lauren...
干嘛  我在这
Yes? Hi! I'm here!
在这 嘿
I'm here. Hi.
Lauren 哦 Lauren......
Lauren. Oh Lauren ...
在Dyson的潜意识里你也在想我？
Wow. Even in Dyson's subconscious you're thinking of me?
医生得一分
Score one for the Doctor.
或者是Dyson在说话?
Unless that's... Dyson talking?
98 97 96
Ninety eight, ninety seven, ninety six,
95......
ninty five...
听上去可不太妙
That can't be good.
谁在那
Who is it?
是我 王子
It is I, the Prince!
你得藏起来
You have to hide.
需要我就说话
Signal if you need me.
我搞得定
I can handle this.
不告诉我个安全词吗?
You don't wanna give me a safe word?
是的 退下
Oui: Back off.
美女！
Cherie!
Filipe王子你好
Why, hello Prince Filipe.
我要鞠躬吗?
Should I bow, or ...
拜托
Please.
我介绍下我自己
Allow me to introduce myself.
我是Filipe王子三世
I am Prince Filipe the Third.
来自Castille
I have traveled from Castille
为了结识你的美丽
to make your delectable acquaintance.
你远道而来
You've come from so far.
让我为你服务吧
Let me lighten your load.
Filipe王子 你喜欢什么?
What do you fancy, Prince Filipe?
你一点时间也不浪费
You do not waste time.
噢
Oh...
时间是小孩儿的把戏
Time is a game played beautifully by children.
我讨厌小孩
I hate children.
聪明的汉子
Hmm... wise man.
我们开始吧
Let's begin.
眼罩？
A blindfold?
拜托 我这么远来看你绽放的花瓣
Please, I've came so far to see your petals in bloom.
你会的 你会的
And you will, you will.
但是未知也相当具有挑逗性
But the unknown can also be so... titillating.
你在搞么子？
What do you think you are doing?
前戏呗
Foreplay?
你不该碰不属于你的东西
You shouldn't touch what doesn't belong to you...
我能搞定他
I had him.
能说声谢谢不
A thank you would suffice.
谢谢侬 不过我们现在手上有被撞呆了的贵族
Thank you, but now we have concussed royalty on our hands.
他的士兵
His soldiers ...
你就告诉他们
Only need to be told
他舟车劳顿正在休息
that he is resting after his long voyage.
晚上要在你这住下
And his night with you.
如果他们来搜查我们怎么办?
What if they search us?
他们绝对想不到查看你的脚
They won't think twice to look at your feet.
开门
Open!
有何贵干？
C'est qui?
我在找王子
I seek the Prince.
他 他现在很忙
He's ...occupied at the moment!
帮我穿上啊
Help me get them on!
刚好合脚 走吧
Perfect fit. Let's go.
你的眼睛
Your eyes ...
现在不是赞美我的时候 我们必须
Now's not a time for compliments, we have to...
Dyson 鞋子好烫
Dyson. It burns...
我被拒绝了
I have been denied.
Helskor不是我的
The Helsk are not intended for me.
开门
Open.
这东西扯不下来
They won't come off!
这些和尚真仔细
Those are some efficient monks.
擦遍姐全身
Didn't miss an inch!
我本来不想说什么的 可是
I wasn't gonna say anything, but...
喂喂 姐爬了半天的下水道管子来救你的菊花
Hey, I crawled through a sewer to rescue your sweet hiney.
就别再那抱怨了
So don't even.
很聪明嘛 伪装你的气味
It's clever. Masking your scent.
对
Yeah.
我很高兴你来了
I'm glad you're here.
至少我不会无聊了
At least now I won't be bored.
就地处死？
Imminent death?
潮湿得头发都打卷的地方？
Hair-frizzing humidity?
好个打盹儿节
What a snoozefest.
跟放了一天假似的
It's kinda like a day off.
难得坐在这里等着被别人救一次 感觉挺不错的
It's nice to sit around and wait to be saved for once.
你难道一点都不害怕吗?
Are you not even a little scared?
我被你震撼了
What I am is impressed.
你居然能在不被人抓住的情况下一路进到这里来
That you managed to get in here without getting caught.
等我们从这里出去以后
When do we get out of here,
我得开始训练你了
I think it's time I start training you.
训练啥?
For what?
成为火影偷者
To be a Shadow Thief.
火影啥？
A Shadow-wha...?
有兴趣？
Interested?
当然啦 听起来像Xbox上的游戏一样
Yeah, It sounds like a freakin' Xbox game.
第一个任务 把那铃声换了
First task: lose the ringtone.
我表 我表训练了
Oh no, I'm out.
臣妾做不到啊
Can't do that.
我可以感觉到Bo
I can feel Bo.
她在我的记忆里
She's in my memories.
你担心她会找到什么吗?
Worried about what she'll find?
这么说吧  如果你和我一样活了那么久......
Let's just say when you've lived as long as I have...
多少会有些后悔事
I've got regrets.
小戴 你真的杀了谁吗?
D, did you actually murder someone?
说来话长
It's a long story.
不管你信不信
Believe it or not
这是一双鞋引发的血案
it starts with a pair of shoes.
听起来像我的故事......
Sounds like my kind of story...
没错
Yeah.
如果是Flora做的这些
If Flora did all this.
为什么指责Dyson?
Why is Dyson being blamed?
55 54 53
Fifty five, fifty four, fifty three
别别别别
No. No, no, no...
这里臭死了
It stinks in here!
亲爱的法国佬 洗个澡吧
Dear period France: wash.
时间快到了
Time's almost up.
你得赶紧剪断那条线
You need to cut the string,
只有你能做到
you're the only one who can do it.
怎么来了个教练
What's with the coach?
你的记忆和Dyson重叠了 你得听我的
Your memories are fusing with Dyson's. You need to listen to me.
不 我还没有得到足够的信息
No! I don't have enough information yet.
我必须知道他为什么被陷害了
I have to find out why he's being framed.
如果你留下来 你就是个瓜娃子
If you stay, you're dumb!
不过我擦 我还是被你震撼了
But damn it, I'm impressed.
你在别人的记忆力停留的时间
You have lasted longer in someone's memory
比我见过的任何人都长
than anyone I've ever seen.
那就帮帮我
Then help me!
你很勇敢
You're brave.
你身上还有别的
And... something else.
别的新的什么
Something new.
你想要为了狼牺牲全部吗?
You sure you want to sacrifice it all for a wolf?
我必须一试
I have to try.
11 10 9 8 7
Eleven, ten, nine, eight, seven ...
3 2 1......
Three, two, one...
他们是真的
They're real.
什么?什么是真的?!
What? What's real?!
你知道这让我面临什么样的危险吗?!
Do you know what kinda danger this puts me in?!
老娘根本不想淌这淌浑水!
I never wanted to see any of this shit!
等等 Bo怎么办?
Wait, what about Bo?
我已经试过把她拽出来了
I tried tapping her out.
结果呢 她留下了
What? She stayed?
是的
Yeah.
等她醒了 第一 给她把衣服准备好
When she wakes up, one: get the straight jacket ready.
第二 就因为那双鞋  你们全都要死了
Two: You're all dead because of those shoes.
什么鞋?等等!
What shoes? Wait!
你必须要回来把她带出来
You have to go back in and get her!
我已经剪断我的线了
I already cut my string.
回到床上 Trick......
Get. In. Bed. Trick...
让他跪舔老娘的奶奶吧 听着
Can suck my left tit! Look...
不管你做什么 不要自己剪掉那红线
whatever you do, don't cut the red string of fate yourself.
明白?
'Kay?
血  好多血......
Blood.So much blood...
Flora 你不想这么做的
Flora. You don't wanna do this.
停不下来
Can't stop.
我也不会停
And I won't stop.
我不想伤害你
I don't wanna hurt you.
这一点也不好玩
Now that's no fun.
因为我想听你抽泣
Because I want to hear you whimper.
拜托了
Please.
为了我好吗?
For me?
我都做了什么?
What have I done?
不是你做的 是鞋
It's not you. It's the shoes.
我身体里的黑暗 所有的黑暗
All the darkest parts of myself... all of them.
这里 现在
Here. Now.
我来帮你脱掉它们
We're going to get you out of this.
鞋子脱不下来
They won't come off. They can't.
它们必须脱下来
Ohh! They have to!
我不想伤害任何人
I don't want to hurt anyone.
我不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you.
我会解决的
I'll fix this.
Flora 醒醒 别走
Flora, stay with me. Stay with me!
我爱你
I love you.
不 你不爱我
No you don't.
我爱森林
My love is the forest.
你呢?
And yours?
我能感觉的你的真爱还没来
I have a feeling that yours is yet to come.
当她来的时候 她会
And when she does, she will be ...
不不 醒醒 Flora
Oh, no, no. Stay with me,
别死
Flora. Stay with me.
我觉得你胡言乱语的时候还好些
I think I liked it better when you were muttering nonsense.
发生什么了?
What's going on?
醒醒 Bo 醒醒
Come on. Wake up, Bo!
Bo 醒醒
Bo, wake up!
Bo 我希望你能看到这个......
Bo, I hope you can see this...
因为我要进来了
Because I'm coming in.
没子弹了吗?
No more bullets?
像你这种臭名远扬的人
A man with a reputation like yours,
所有人都会觉得是你
everyone will think it was you.
不......
No...
把鞋给我
Give me the shoes.
不
No.
你做了什么?
What did you do?
有人给我了明确的指示
I was provided with explicit instructions.
不计任何代价拿到鞋子
Get shoes. Whatever the cost.
逃跑
Now run.
就像你一贯的作风
Like you have always done.
把鞋留下
Leave the shoes behind.
你杀了她
You killed her.
死亡
Mortis.
吾寻之
Invenio.
大一统
In unitate.
你不在乎这个女人
You don't care about this woman.
除了你自己 你没在乎过任何人
You have never cared about anyone but yourself.
1864年 鹿特丹  燃起博伊曼斯美术馆的大火
Rotterdam 1864,the fire at Boijmans.
*1864年的大火烧毁了博伊曼斯博物馆所有艺术品，只有127件艺术品幸存，其中有画作在大火中丢失*
1817年 伦敦 你牵扯入格雷格尔贩卖岛国的骗局
London 1817, your implication in the Poyais scheme.
*Poyais：格雷格尔声称自己是"Poyais"，一个虚构的国家的主人，欺骗了大量移民投资者前往该岛*
你欺骗过的无数的男人
The countless men you conned,
羞辱过的无数的女人
the women you shamed.
闭嘴
Be quiet!
你活着就是浪费生命
You are a waste of flesh.
你就只会偷东西乱搞
All you have ever done is steal and screw.
现在你的自私杀死了Flora
And now your selfishness has killed Flora.
事实上 我们就指望这个呢
In fact, we were counting on this.
你说的没错
You're right.
都是我的错
This is all my fault.
现在你可以继续你之前的生活
Now you can resume your life as it was.
走吧
Go on.
跑吧
Run.
走吧  跑吧
"Go on. Run..."
一开始我还真考虑过
For a second, I considered it.
为什么 你是无辜的
Why? You were innocent.
我不是 是我干的
I wasn't. I did it.
我杀了Flora
I killed Flora.
Crater杀了她
Crater shot her.
是我让她穿上那双鞋
I was the one who made her put on those shoes.
就因为我 她杀了那些人
Because of me, she killed those people.
因为我 她被杀了
Because of me, she was killed.
Dyson 你那时不知道
Dyson. You didn't know.R
但我以为我知道
But I thought I did.
我的自大 无知
My arrogance, my ignorance.
都是我的罪孽
That was my crime.
我过去种下的恶因结恶果了 Kenzi
And the past has caught up to me, Kenzi.
接下来发生了什么
What happened next?
把鞋子给我
Give me the shoes.
走吧
Be free.
如果你觉得我会让你和你那爱谁谁的主人
If you think I will let you and your masters,
拥有这种邪恶的东西
whoever they may be, possess this sort of evil.
那么你错了
You are mistaken.
你想要 Helskor 先得从我的尸体上跨过去
If you want The Helskor, you're gonna have to kill me first.
哈
Hah!
让我猜猜  你也是为了鞋子而来的
Let me guess, you're here for the shoes too?
我从来不想要它们
I never wanted them.
我是在为新世界找寻一个副手
I seek a second for the New World.
谁的副手
Second to whom?
如果你感兴趣的话
If you are interested
破晓以前到我的祷告室见我
meet me in my prayer room before dawn.
我总是想像我会去汽车旅馆的泳池边
I always imagined I'd go motel pool-side.
你懂啦  一手绞绞糖
You know...Twizzler in one hand.
一手Liam Neeson
Liam Neeson in the other.
*著名演员 曾主演<辛德勒的名单>等电影*
你在发抖
You're shaking.
准时可不是Bo擅长的技能
Bo's greatest skill has never been her punctuality, you know?
她把我一个人丢给蛇精病客户多少次了?
The number of times she left me alone with a crazy client?
不过当事关紧要的时候 她总是会来的
But when it matters, she always makes it.
她总是会摆平一切的
She always saves the day.
对吧
Right?
还没完呢 Kenzi
It's not over yet, Kenzi.
死亡
Mortis.
吾寻之
Invenio.
大一统
In unitate.
你没有遵守异种神圣的法规
You have failed to abide by the sacred rules of the Fae.
你还有什么遗言赶紧说吧
If you have any last words, speak them now.
额滴神 额滴神啊
Oh-god-oh-god-oh-god.
那么人类帮你说了
The human has spoken for you, then.
我把你最后遗言的机会都偷了
I just stole your last words?
艾马 我真讨厌
Oh my god, I suck!
把人类放了 我就给你Helskor
Release the human and I'll give you The Helskor!
Dyson 你不能那样做
Dyson, you can't do that.
我救不了Flora
I couldn't save Flora.
可我能救你
But I can save you.
这么多年了
After all these years,
我们怎么相信你还知道鞋的下落
why should we trust you know of their location?
因为我拥有其中一只
Because I have one in my possession.
把Kenzi放了 我就告诉你们第二只在哪里
Release Kenzi, and I will reveal the location of the second.
你刚做了什么?
What did you just do?
没人需要再受你受过的折磨了
No one will ever suffer again, as you did.
我会把这些鞋子藏起来
I will hide the shoes.
藏到没人会找的地方
Somewhere no one will ever look...
Bo
Bo.
不是吧
It's not you.
你才死了
You died.
我刚刚才把你埋了
I had to bury you!
那确实不是我 你给搞糊涂了
Well that's not me. You're getting confused.
不!
No!
你的记忆开始融合了
Bo, your memories are melding, Bo.
你想要什么?!
Hey! What do you want?!
你想跟我说什么?
What are you trying to tell me?
Dyson的冠军腰带吗?
Dyson's championship belt?
我不懂那是什么
I don't know what that means!
Bobo 你得试试这个
Bobo, you've got to try this.
软糖坚果 冷冰冰的 放你嘴里
Fudgy nuts. Cold. Inyomouth.
Kenzi
Kenzi.
这是怎么了?
What's happening?
你得回现实中
You have to come back!
你必须剪掉你的红线  Bo
You have to cut your red string, Bo.
你走了 没什么值得我回去的
You're gone. There's nothing to come back for.
你还有Dyson
There's Dyson.
他需要你
He needs you.
Dyson
Dyson...
他想告诉我什么......
He's trying to tell me something...
我知道
I know ...
不不 不不不不
No no... no no no no.
人类不能进去的  Lauren! Lauren!
A human can't be in there. Lauren! Lauren!
我擦 那我怎么把你带出去?
Oh, shit! Then how do I get you out?
别剪线
Don't cut the string.
剪线
Cut the string.
Bo?
Bo 我把我的线剪了
Bo, I cut my string.
你还是你吗?
Are you still you?
说话呀
Say something.
我知道怎么救Dyson了
I know how to save Dyson.
他们搜查了你说的地方
They have checked your location.
没有Helskor
There is no Helskor.
找个地图 书呆子她七舅姥姥
Get a map, dweebs.
我已经先拿了
I just got to it first.
在你封起来的冠军皮带里面找到的
Found it encased in your framed championship belt.
用苏格兰皮带捆着的
Also, wrapped in a jock strap.
很干净
It was clean.
跟霍金兄一样聪明
Stephen Hawking clever.
把Dyson和Kenzi放了 我就把你的破鞋还你
Set Dyson and Kenzi free and you get the stank shoe
死亡
Mortis
吾寻之
invenio
大一统
in unetate.
你
You.
是你
你命令让Crater不计任何代价拿到鞋子
You ordered Crater to get the shoes. Whatever the cost.
她真是出乎我们预料
She is...more than we expected.
恭喜你终于领悟了
Well, glad you finally got the memo.
Dyson没有罪 没有杀人
Dyson's not guilty or murder.
你才是犯罪的那个
You are.
现在 你想要鞋子吗?
Now, do you want the shoe or not?
恩 尝起来像暖暖黏黏的爱
Mhm. It tastes like warm squishy love.
你说热狗还是自由
The hot dog or freedom?
恩
Mhm.
真是好险 千钧一发
That was close. Too close.
我就是喜欢差一点
And I usually like close.
险中求胜
A close shave.
命悬一线
Glenn Close.
和外星人亲密接触
Close Encounters of the Third Kind.
阿门
Amen.
你知道不 神经外科
You know? Neurosurgery?
小菜一碟
I can do.
走路和吃饭
Walking and eating?
对我来说有难度
I struggle with.
不是我想说点俗套的
You know... not to get all cheese-dog or anything,
但是小伙伴们我们又欢聚一堂了
but guys, the gang's is all back together!
某人在某个地方 给我们牵上了命运的红线
Someone, somewhere tied a Red String of Fate around all of us.
阿门
Amen.
Bo 根据传说 红线只给两个人牵的
Bo, according to legend, that's only intended for two people.
我不管
I don't care.
反正我在里面晕晕的
It makes me feel fuzzy inside.
好像我们就该是在一起的
Like we all belong together.
命运也就这么点用了
Destiny only takes you so far.
要在一起还需要好多努力
Actually staying together takes work.
你穿这和尚袍子可爱死了
You look damn cute in those monk robes.
苦行僧袍子的恋物癖
Friar Tuck fetish?
性感哦
Hot!
好吧 嚼你的食物 吞下去
Oh. Okay...Chew, swallow.
你很安静
You're quiet.
太亲密了
That was intimate.
你进入了我里面一次
You. In me, for once.
这话说的
Such a way with words.
我能感觉到你
I could feel you.
不知不觉还送给你一个线索
Sent you a message without even knowing it.
我好高兴你明白了
I'm glad you got it.
我们的思想挺合拍
Our minds work well together.
那确实
Yes they do.
嘿狼叔
Hey D man!
你埋葬了Flora后发生了什么?
What happened after you buried Flora?
我没想到你会来
I didn't think you would come.
我没法救她
I couldn't save her.
你努力了
You tried.
努力是不够的
Trying is not enough.
努力不能让她复活
Trying doesn't bring her back.
我一无是处
I am worthless.
不 你只是迷失了
No.You have just been... lost.
我也是
And so have I.
我不想再打仗了
I don't wanna fight anymore.
再不想有武器 战争了
No more weapons, no more wars.
我们会创造异种殖民地 更好的生活
We will start a Fae colony. A better life.
新的开始 一起
A new start... together.
为什么是我
Why me?
你的赤子之心
You're pure of heart.
一个士兵
A soldier.
一个变形者
A shifter.
你知道？
You know?
你效命于Alieach王
You served The King of Alieach.
被他背叛了
Were betrayed.
脱离了狼群
Broke free from your pack.
成了独狼
Went lone wolf.
可行善并非一人之力能成
But we cannot do good alone.
不论我们有多强
No matter how powerful we may seem.
血圣
The Blood King.
可你消失很久了
But you disappeared long ago.
大家都以为你死了
Many think you are dead.
我希望这样最好
I'd like to keep it that way.
你是个英雄 Dyson
You are a hero, Dyson.
板上钉钉
It is written.
这是你的命运
It is your destiny.
没有行动 命运一文不值
Destiny is nothing without action...
我向你宣告我的忠诚  血圣
I swear fealty to you, Blood King.
看看你现在
Well, look how you turned out,
经常充当救人英雄
saving our tight butts all the time.
Trick才真是救人于危难之中
Trick is the true savior.
最近对我来说不是
Not to me. Not lately.
别这么说
That's not fair.
他还不知道你胸上记号的事
He doesn't know about the mark on your chest.
你胸上的啥记号?
What mark on your chest?
根本不是重点 我是说......
That's besides the point.I mean...
我已经受够小心翼翼了
I'm done tiptoeing around this.
他是血王 是我的亲外公
He's the Blood King. He's my Grandfather.
他干嘛不帮我想想我为什么被带走了?
Why hasn't he helped me figure out why I was taken?
他总是想保护你
He's always trying to protect you.
扯淡
Bullshit.
他是被什么吓到了
He's scared of something.
我知道你们不想承认
I know you guys don't want to admit it,
但是你们都看到了
but you've seen it!
我知道
I know you have.
鞋子 流浪者
The Shoes. The One Who Wanders.
你和Trick怎么以前都没告诉我?!
Why didn't you or Trick tell me about this connection before?!
因为我到现在才想起来
Because I couldn't remember until now.
有些东西把记忆屏蔽了
Something blacked it out.
是啊 最近这事真是屡见不鲜
Yeah well, there seems to be a lot of that going around.
我们得找到流浪者
We need to find The Wanderer.
弄清楚他干嘛绑架我
Find out why he took me.
我为什么变黑暗了
Why I'm Dark.
我们怎么才能找到他
How are we getting to him?
有个他想要的东西
There's something he wants.
他一直想要的东西
Something that he's always wanted.
Dyson  第二只Hel鞋在哪?
Dyson, where's that second Hel-shoe?
我给了Angel
I gave it to Angel.
酒保？
The bartender?
是个见习变形者
And fellow shifter.
我让她逃跑
I told her to flee.
藏着鞋子
Keep it hidden.
等待真的英雄
Wait for the True hero.
我觉得我们都等够了
Well, I think we're all done waiting.
我要出发了
'Cause here I come.